we're gonna talk about auctions in this
我们将在此谈论拍卖
segment and when we think about auctions
细分以及当我们考虑拍卖时
we usually think about something fairly
我们通常会公平考虑
specific often something fairly simple
具体往往很简单
this is probably what many of us think
这可能是我们许多人的想法
of when we think about auctions
当我们考虑拍卖的时候
initially an art auction where the
最初是艺术品拍卖，
auctioneer displays the art and people
拍卖师展示艺术品和人物
from the audience
听众
call out larger and larger numbers until
喊出越来越大的数字，直到
nobody says anything and the auctioneer
没有人说什么，拍卖师
famously says going once going twice
著名的说一次去两次
sold and that's this that's how the sale
出售，这就是销售的方式
is decided on somewhat differently is
决定的有所不同是
this what is this well this is the
这是什么好这是
flower market in Holland just outside
荷兰的花卉市场就在外面
Amsterdam and here every day large
阿姆斯特丹和这里每天都很大
number of flowers are trucked in and
运了一些花，
Seoul's sold rather quickly because
首尔的销量很快，因为
flowers are perishable and they're sold
花易腐烂，被卖掉
somewhat differently there is a trading
有所不同，有交易
pit where the pallets of flowers are
鲜花托盘所在的坑
rolled in and they are auctioned off
卷入，它们被拍卖掉
auctioned off rather differently you see
拍卖会与众不同
these large clocks in the background and
这些大钟在后台
they have a special role and what that
他们扮演着特殊的角色
is something to be discussed here it's a
这里要讨论的是
very different kind of auction these are
这些是非常不同的拍卖
auctions for the rights to use our
拍卖使用我们的权利
electric magnetic spectrum so our
电磁频谱所以我们
airwaves are filled with all kind of
电波充满了各种
broadcasts from television to Cellular
从电视广播到手机
to what-have-you and those are worth a
对你有什么，那些都值得
lot to commercially and socially so
在商业上和社会上都是如此
governments all over the world have
全世界的政府都有
auctioned off the rights to use this
拍卖使用权
spectrum famously starting with the u.s.
频谱始于美国
FCC or Federal Communication Commission
FCC或联邦通讯委员会
besides being valuable to society and
除了对社会有价值
fetching very large sums in the billions
取得数十亿美元的巨额款项
these altars very interesting because
这些祭坛非常有趣，因为
they're complicated what's being sold
他们很复杂正在出售什么
here is not something as simple as a
这不是一个简单的东西
single piece piece of art or even a
一件艺术品，甚至一件
palette of flowers
花的调色板
what sold here are regions and
这里卖的是地区和
frequencies and so different regions in
频率等不同区域
the country are different goods and in
这个国家是不同的商品
each region one can broadcast at
每个地区都可以在
different frequencies so that makes for
不同的频率，因此
a different kind of auction where both
另一种拍卖方式
the design of the auction and the
拍卖的设计和
trading in the auction are non-trivial
拍卖中的交易是不平凡的
and finally in all those cases until now
最后在所有这些情况下直到现在
we've had a single seller and main
我们有一个卖方和主要
buyers here's a famous example we have
买家，这是一个著名的例子
many cells and many buyers this is the
许多细胞和许多买家，这是
Nasdaq one of the many stock exchanges
纳斯达克众多证券交易所之一
in the world we have many buyers and is
在世界上，我们有很多买家
very sellers of goods and in fact these
非常商品的卖家，实际上这些
Goods coming multiple units if you wish
如果您愿意的话，货品有多个单位
to buy Google stock then you can buy
买谷歌股票然后你可以买
many such shares and there are many
很多这样的股份，还有很多
others like you want to buy it and many
其他像您想购买的东西
many who want to sell it so the way you
许多人想以您的方式出售它
design a two-sided exchange and the way
设计双向交流和方式
you trade in it and again different from
您进行交易，再次与
the simple single sided option we know
我们知道的简单的单面选项
these are all examples of auctions there
这些都是那里的拍卖的例子
are many other examples and the theory
还有很多其他例子和理论
about how to design and how to be able
关于如何设计和如何能够
option is very rich
选项非常丰富